Generals!
Are you all right?
Queen Echidna!
We're in danger! My spells aren't working,
and strange things keep happening!
I've encountered strange happenings as well.
I cannot find anyone in this inn.
Not the innkeep nor her staff.
It's as if they never existed to begin with.
N-no...
I know it's difficult to believe, but it's likely a ghost.
Where are the other three Generals?
You didn't run into them?!
No.
Wait, three?
Lily?! Hey, Lily! Where'd you go?!
D-did the ghost take Lily!?
This is growing dire.
Shutina! Leo! We must find our colleagues at once!
Yes, ma'am!
Remember, the Work Trip is First and Foremost a Learning Opportunity (Part 2)
The place really is deserted.
We've definitely searched the whole inn now.
You're right. The only place left would be...
Here. I just hope that everyone is all right.
If I could cast spells, I'd blow away every ghost
in this inn with a single spell...
That spell might blow away everything else, too!
Doesn't look like anyone's here...
Yeah.
This keeps me safe, this keeps me safe...
Good on you for wearing it.
Queen Echidna!
Are these the only sizes they had for these?
I dunno if it's too tight,
but my head kinda hurts wearing it.
They're one size fits all.
Then why does my head hurt?
I couldn't say.
Besides, the others were wearing it,
and they got spirited away.
But you two are safe! I'm glad you kept them with you.
Echidna, are you...
No, the ghost has me!
Shutina!
H-help!
Echidna?
Now...
There's only one left!
Echidna?
Screw you, 'ghost'! Where'd you take my allies?!
Dammit, get back here!
Show me who you are, you bastard!
What?
Ta-dah.
Hooray, you've been pranked.
You've Been Pranked!
We totally got him!
REALLY?
Hey, can I swim in here? Is that okay?
No swimming in the bath!
I would've never guessed it was all set up by our Queen!
I knew you were hiding something.
An award-winning performance, if I do say so myself.
T'was my grand plan to prank you with a haunting tale!
Haunting Prank
Or t'was the innkeeps, as she put
that interesting option on the check-in list.
I couldn't have done it without Mernes' help.
There was only so much I could do on my own.
Is that why you FORCED me to help?
Oh yeah, how'd you guys get caught?
I got caught by a trap.
Mernes grabbed me.
When I turned a corner, I fell into a pitfall trap.
I took a nap!
So that's why you're sober.
Yup!
You all had such wonderful reactions.
It was super fun! I really thought
there was a ghost haunting us!
I was quite scared, especially since I couldn't cast magic!
How'd you do that, by the way?
Was it the headbands?
Correct!
They didn't ward off spirits, but they are a type of artifact.
They interfere with waves in the brain
and prevent magic from being cast.
Though they don't appear to work
on individuals who are intoxicated.
Are there any side effects to worry about?
Of course not!
I am your Demon Queen. I wouldn't harm
my underlings for the sake of a prank.
Huh. All right.
I apologize if you were frightened.
I AM a Demon Queen, after all.
This went a little too far for a harmless prank, though.
Really? The man who nearly killed
all of us doesn't want us to 'go too far'?
Besides, this experience will futher strengthen
our team's bonds. Doing that is part of my job.
That's right! You're so cool, Echidna!
I guess I got to see Leo make some good faces.
I don't see any problem with having
a bit of fun like this every now and then!
Cheer up, Leo. The innkeep
has gifted us some fireworks.
Let us enjoy them after our bath.
Ooh, fireworks! I can't wait!
Yay!
So pretty!
Wow!
Mernes, do you have a sparkler?
It's tradition to do a sparkler at the end.
Is this a sparkler? It's my first time,
so I don't know what any of them are called.
Wait, this is your first time? You'll like this one.
Thanks.
Hot, hot!
Ooh, wow!
Why would you think I'd like this?
Huh? It's not to your liking?
Well, Leo?
You haven't traveled for pleasure in quite a while, yes?
It's nice to spend some time with your friends, too.
Yeah.
Gotta end with these!
I really think you'll like these.
It's not bad.
Bokura no kokoro wa itsudatte moroi
Our hearts are always so frail and fragile
Sore demo mae o muite nagai michi o susumu
But we still face forward and continue down our long road
Shiranakatta koto wa kore kara shireba ii
If we don't know something now, we can go learn about it
Tsuzukeru koto no saki ni aru mono ima wa mada wakaranai kedo
We might not know what's at the end of our long, continuing journey
Hitori de kakaekomi suginaide tama ni wa senaka o azuketemiyou
Don't try to do everything yourself, lean on us sometimes
Yowasa ni yorisoeru no mo tsuyosanara
Sharing your weaknesses is strength in itself
Madamada saki wa nagai kui no nai you ni
There's still a long way to go,
so make sure you won't regret anything
Hashiridase riyuu wa tanjun
Dash on! The reason's simple
Tokihanate risou no yume o
Let loose! Make your dreams reality
Fumidashita saki no mirai wa jibun shidai de dou ni demo naru
The future you're heading towards is one you shape yourself
Kawaru koto ga kowakunattemo sukoshizutsu de iinda
It's okay to be scared of change, you can go little by little
Taisetsu na mono o mamoru tame ni
I want to protect the things I cherish
Megurimegutte tsunagatta
(I'm so glad we found each other)
Kimi ni arigatou todoiteimasu you ni
So I hope you hear how thankful I am for you